 export const quizData = [
		{
			subject: "General Knowledge",
			questions: [
				{
					id: 1,
					question: "Which country is regarded as the 'Giant of Africa'?",
					optionA: "Egypt",
					optionB: "Kenya",
					optionC: "Nigeria",
					optionD: "South Africa",
					correctAnswer: "Nigeria",
				},

				{
					id: 2,
					question: "What is the capital state of Russia?",
					optionA: "Kremlin",
					optionB: "Saint Petersburg",
					optionC: "Kiev",
					optionD: "Moscow",
					correctAnswer: "Moscow",
				},

				{
					id: 3,
					question: "Who is the first man to step foot on the moon?",
					optionA: "Yuri Gaganrin",
					optionB: "Neil Armstrong",
					optionC: "Elon Musk",
					optionD: "Edwin Adrin",
					correctAnswer: "Neil Armstrong",
				},

				{
					id: 4,
					question: "What year did World War 2 ended?",
					optionA: "1945",
					optionB: "1948",
					optionC: "1942",
					optionD: "1947",
					correctAnswer: "1945",
				},

				{
					id: 5,
					question: "Which of this countries is a world nuclear superpower",
					optionA: "South Africa",
					optionB: "Russia",
					optionC: "United Arab Emirates",
					optionD: "Malaysia",
					correctAnswer: "Russia",
				},
			],
		},

		{
			subject: "Biology",
			questions: [
				{
					id: 1,
					question: "The father of Zoology is?",
					optionA: "Aristotle",
					optionB: "Linnaeus",
					optionC: "Whittalker",
					optionD: "John Ray",
					correctAnswer: "Aristotle",
				},

				{
					id: 2,
					question: "Throughout the world, official species names are in?",
					optionA: "Latin",
					optionB: "Greek",
					optionC: "French",
					optionD: "English",
					correctAnswer: "Latin",
				},

				{
					id: 3,
					question: "Trypanosomiasis is transmitted by?",
					optionA: "Mosquitoes",
					optionB: "Glossina",
					optionC: "Housefly",
					optionD: "All of the above",
					correctAnswer: "Glossina",
				},

				{
					id: 4,
					question: "Who suggested that 'All plants are made of cells'?",
					optionA: "Hooke",
					optionB: "Schwann",
					optionC: "Schneider",
					optionD: "Virchow",
					correctAnswer: "Schneider",
				},

				{
					id: 5,
					question:
						"The interaction of living and non-living things is termed?",
					optionA: "Enviromental Biology",
					optionB: "Ecology",
					optionC: "Ecosystem",
					optionD: "nature",
					correctAnswer: "Ecosystem",
				},

				{
					id: 6,
					question: "Throughout the world, official soecies names are in?",
					optionA: "Latin",
					optionB: "Greek",
					optionC: "French",
					optionD: "English",
					correctAnswer: "Latin",
				},

				{
					id: 7,
					question: "Who suggested that 'All plants are made of cells'?",
					optionA: "Hooke",
					optionB: "Schwann",
					optionC: "Schneider",
					optionD: "Virchow",
					correctAnswer: "Schneider",
				},
			],
		},
		{
			subject: "Mathematics",
			questions: [
				{
					id: 1,
					question: "What is the next Prime number after 13?",
					optionA: "14",
					optionB: "19",
					optionC: "17",
					optionD: "12",
					correctAnswer: "17",
				},

				{
					id: 2,
					question: "1,8,15,22,29,36,... is?",
					optionA: "G.P",
					optionB: "Arithmetic Series",
					optionC: "Geometric Series",
					optionD: "A.P",
					correctAnswer: "A.P",
				},

				{
					id: 3,
					question: "Every even integer is also a/an ?",
					optionA: "Natural number",
					optionB: "Rational number",
					optionC: "Whole number",
					optionD: "All of the above",
					correctAnswer: "Rational number",
				},

				{
					id: 4,
					question: "The set {{1, 2, 3}, {4, 5}} has how many elements?",
					optionA: "2",
					optionB: "Infinite",
					optionC: "1",
					optionD: "5",
					correctAnswer: "5",
				},

				{
					id: 5,
					question: "Solve 3 + 6 x ( 5 + 4 ) / 3 - 7",
					optionA: "14",
					optionB: "16",
					optionC: "11",
					optionD: "15",
					correctAnswer: "14",
				},

				{
					id: 6,
					question: "Every even integer is also a/an ?",
					optionA: "Natural number",
					optionB: "Rational number",
					optionC: "Whole number",
					optionD: "All of the above",
					correctAnswer: "Rational number",
				},
			],
		},
 ];
